A Guide to the Herbert E. Harris II Papers
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Series III: Legislation Files
  - Subseries A: Legislative Information Files
    - HR 11338: Cosponsored - To designate certain lands in the National Forest System as Wilderness (Box Box 78)
    - HR 11369: Cosponsored - To improve the coordination of economic policy making within the Federal government (Box Box 78)
    - HR 11526: Cosponsored - To change the name of the Dulles International Airport (Box Box 78)
    - HR 11796: Cosponsored - To provide a Solar & Conservation Loan Program within the Small Business Administration (Box Box 78)
    - HR 11813: Cosponsored - To provide automatic Cost Of Living adjustments in income tax and withholding rates (Box Box 78)
    - HR 11984: Cosponsored - To provide for use of professional services under Medicare & Medicaid programs (Box Box 78)
    - HR 11978: Cosponsored - To allow Federal employees to meet the obligations of their faith (Box Box 78)
    - HR 12155: Cosponsored - To provide for merit selection of U.S. attorneys (Box Box 78)
    - HR 12443: Cosponsored - To establish a select Commission on Immigration & Refugee Policy (Box Box 78)
    - HR 12508: Cosponsored - 5/2/78 Amend Immigration Act/ adopted children (Box Box 78)
    - HR 12512: Cosponsored - To require the Federal Aviation Administration to put into effect noise abatement plans for airports (Box Box 78)
    - HR 12663: Cosponsored - 5/10/78 Establish Potomac River Commission (Box Box 78)
    - HR 12670: Cosponsored - 5/10/78 Facilitate transition, energy to solar energy (Box Box 78)
    - HR 12876: Cosponsored - 5/25/78 Establish Solar Energy Development Bank (Box Box 78)
    - HR 12924: no description (Box Box 78)
    - HR 13349: Cosponsored - 6/29/78 Repeal sections of title III of Immigration (Box Box 78)
    - HR 13369: Cosponsored - 6/29/78 Amend provisions of title 39 (Box Box 78)
    - HR 13421: Cosponsored - 7/11/78 Amend Indochina Migration/ Refugee Ass. Act of 1975 (Box Box 78)
    - HR 13434: Cosponsored - 7/2/78 Provide consistent standards in Federal Court (Box Box 78)
    - HR 13963: Cosponsored - 8/17/78 Establish to provide procedures for civil court enforcement of congressional court subpoenas (Box Box 78)
    - HR 14012: Sponsored - 9/7/78 Amend National Capital Transportation Act of 1969 (Box Box 78)
    - HR 1: Cosponsored - 1/15/79 Campaign financing for House of Representatives (Box Box 78)
    - HR 10: Cosponsored - 1/5/79 Institutionalized Persons Rights (Box Box 78)
    - HR 15: Cosponsored - 1/5/79 Martin Luther King - National Holiday Bill (Box Box 78)
    - HR 39: Cosponsored - Provide for the designation and conservation of certain public lands (Box Box 78)
    - HR 65: Cosponsored - 5/2/79 Legislative Oversight Act "Sunset Leg" (Box Box 78)
    - HR 100: Cosponsored - 3/18/80 Discrimination in insurance (Box Box 78)
    - HR 165: Cosponsored - 1/15/79 Amend the Social Security Act (Box Box 78)
    - HR 272: Cosponsored - 3/26/79 Provide greater equity in the program - excludes value of family residence from eligibility calculations (Box Box 78)
    - HR 277: Cosponsored - 1/15/79 Regulating electric rates; Federal, State, and Local level (Box Box 79)
    - HR 290: Cosponsored - 6/4/79 Sludge Management Bill (Box Box 79)
    - HR 365: Cosponsored - 5/4/79 Tax indexing proposal (Box Box 79)
    - HR 605: Cosponsored - 2/22/79 Solar Energy Development Bank (Box Box 79)
    - HR 769: Cosponsored - 4/10/79 To extend domestic oil price controls for a period of months (20) (Box Box 79)
    - HR 827: Cosponsored - 1/15/79 Postal Reorganization Act - Disputes (Box Box 79)
    - HR 997: Cosponsored - 6/8/79 The Sound Recording Performance Rights Amendment (Box Box 79)
    - HR 1114: Cosponsored - 6/4/79 Arts and Humanities Checkoff Bill (Box Box 79)
    - HR 1297: Cosponsored - 3/4/80 Interstate trade-steel jaw traps (Box Box 79)
    - HR 1437: Cosponsored - 2/2/79 To force the "subpoena first rule" (Box Box 79)
    - HR 1539: Cosponsored - Allow commercial banks to underwrite revenue bonds (Box Box 79)
    - HR 1714: Cosponsored - 2/8/79 Fuel Adjustment Clause Prohibition Act (Box Box 79)
    - HR 1986: Cosponsored - 5/4/79 FAA police (airport) under the provisions of sec. 1114, title 15, U.S. code (Box Box 79)
    - HR 2126: Cosponsored - 2/13/79 Amend the Food Stamp Act of 1977 (Box Box 79)
    - HR 2129: Cosponsored - 6/7/79 To address monopolistic practices in professional sports (Box Box 79)
    - HR 2156: Cosponsored - 4/11/79 '79 Oil Import Purchasing Authority Act (Box Box 79)
    - HR 2209: Cosponsored - 2/15/79 Sale Representatives Protection Act (Box Box 79)
    - HR 2305: Cosponsored - 2/27/79 Franchise Reform Act (Box Box 79)
    - HR 2400: Cosponsored - 11/14/79 Postal Service Employees' Political Activities Act of 1979 (Box Box 79)
    - HR 2472: Cosponsored - 3/13/80 Health care for divorced military spouse (Box Box 79)
    - HR 2444: Cosponsored - 2/27/79 Establish a Department of Education (Box Box 79)
    - HR 2542: Cosponsored - 2/7/80 Revise tax credit for the elderly (Box Box 79)
    - HR 2546: Sponsored - 3/1/79 Mobile Teachers Retirement Assistance Act (Box Box 79)
    - HR 2570: Cosponsored - 11/30/79 Ends outside earnings limit on Social Security (Box Box 79)
    - HR 2602: Cosponsored - 4/24/79 Certification for those companies who sell health to the elderly (Box Box 79)
    - HR 2694: Cosponsored - 7/12/79 Mandatory Retirement Bill FSO (Box Box 79)
    - HR 2748: Sponsored - 3/8/79 Improvement of Firefighting Personnel workweek (Box Box 79)
    - HR 2792: Cosponsored - 7/30/79 Condominium Tenants Bill (Box Box 79)
    - HR 2815: Cosponsored - 3/30/79 Diversification Act of '79 -- assistance for DPV; nations in to increase alternative energy production (Box Box 79)
    - HR 2847: Sponsored - 3/13/79 Social Security Tax Reduction Act of 1979 (Box Box 79)
    - HR 2973: Cosponsored - 3/16/79 The Citizens' Postal Rate Relief Act of 1979 (Box Box 79)
    - HR 3085: Cosponsored - 7/13/79 Eliminate marriage tax (Box Box 79)
    - HR 3100: Cosponsored - 3/20/79 Limit amount of outside earned income (Box Box 79)
    - HR 3245: Cosponsored - 7/23/79 (introduced 3/27/79) IRS Bill; Independent Contractor tax stations bill (Box Box 79)
    - HR 3271: Sponsored - 3/27/79 Amend the Anti-trust Civil Process Act (Box Box 79)
    - HR 3336: Cosponsored - 3/29/79 Amend the 1945 Washington, D.C. Redevelopment (Box Box 79)
    - HR 3379: Sponsored - 4/2/79 Amend Title 2 of Social Security Act (Box Box 79)
    - HR 3560: Cosponsored - 4/10/79 Retirement Benefits for Washington, D.C. (Box Box 79)
    - HR 3611, 3612: Cosponsored - 6/11/79 Food Security Act of 1979 (Box Box 79)
    - HR 3621: Cosponsored - 4/10/79 Maintain price controls on oil (Box Box 79)
    - HR 3635: Cosponsored - 10/29/79 Waiting period for disability (Box Box 79)
    - HR 3723: Cosponsored - 2/16/79 Aviation noise abatement policy (Box Box 79)
    - HR 3769: Cosponsored - 4/26/79 Amend the Higher Education Act of '65 (Box Box 79)
    - HR 3824: Cosponsored - 5/1/79 Authorized the Council of Washington, D.C. to issue revenue bonds (Box Box 79)
    - HR 3909: Cosponsored - 5/3/79 Amend sec. 12 of the Contract Disputes Act of 1978 (Box Box 79)
    - HR 3914: Cosponsored - 5/3/79 Amend National Capital Transportation Act of 1969 (Box Box 79)
    - HR 3930: Cosponsored - 5/3/79 Defense Production Act Bill (Box Box 79)
    - HR 3939: Cosponsored - 5/3/79 Washington, D.C. Retirement Benefits (Box Box 79)
    - HR 3951: Cosponsored - 5/4/79 METRO (Box Box 79)
    - HR 3958: Cosponsored - 5/7/79 Prohibit discrimination against gasohol distributors (Box Box 79)
    - HR 4095: Sponsored - 5/14/79 Amend the Internal Revenue Code of '54 higher education (Box Box 79)
    - HR 4120: Cosponsored - 5/16/79 Medical and shelter expense deductions (Box Box 79)
    - HR 4128: Cosponsored - 6/7/79 Eliminate preferences which the oil & gas industry has in the tax code (Box Box 79)
    - HR 4285: Gelb Private Bill (Box Box 79)
    - HR 4294: Sponsored - 6/4/79 Amend the Immigration and Nationality Act (Box Box 79)
    - HR 4295: Cosponsored - 6/6/79 Energy Anti-monopoly Act of 1979 (Box Box 79)
    - HR 4358: Cosponsored - 6/25/80 Spinal Cord Rejuvenation Research Act (Box Box 79)
    - HR 4395: Cosponsored - 6/8/79 Require public disclosure of lobbying and related activities (Box Box 79)
    - HR 4546: Cosponsored - 6/20/79 Amend the Washington, D.C. Redevelopment Act (Box Box 79)
    - HR 4568: Cosponsored - 7/21/79 Amend the Defense Production Act (Box Box 79)
    - HR 4647: Cosponsored -10/10/79 Armed Forces Earned Education Assistance Act (Box Box 79)
    - HR 4655: Cosponsored - 6/28/79 Amend title 28 in the U.S. Code to provide for improvements in the administration of courts (Box Box 79)
    - HR 4717: Sponsored -7/10/79 Contracting out - obligation of funds by agencies (Box Box 79)
    - HR 4748: Cosponsored - 7/11/79 Amend the Clayton Act to stop the growth of monopolies of oil companies (Box Box 79)
    - HR 4796: Cosponsored - 8/17/79 Tax Exclusion for overseas workers (Box Box 79)
    - HR 4825: Sponsored - 7/17/79 Nuclear Sabotage Bill (Box Box 79)
    - HR 4970: Cosponsored - 7/26/79 Federal Election Campaign Act/ Campaign Contribution Reform Act (Box Box 79)
    - HR 4981: Cosponsored - 7/26/79 Citizens' Commission for the Commemoration of the Federal Government bicentennial (Box Box 79)
    - HR 4986: Cosponsored - 7/24/79 Permit credit unions to offer share-draft accounts and allow NOW accounts (Box Box 79)
    - HR 5005: Spaulding Private Bill (Box Box 79)
    - HR 5099: Cosponsored - 10/29/79 Sales Representatives Protection Act (Box Box 79)
    - HR 5138: Cosponsored - 8/2/79 Appropriations for OEM, MSPB, FLRA (Box Box 79)
    - HR 5151: Cosponsored - 10/23/79 Dental Insurance Program for Federal employees (Box Box 79)
    - HR 5184: Cosponsored - 9/5/79 To amend Internal Revenue Code (Box Box 79)
    - HR 5226: Craig Private Bill (Box Box 79)
    - HR 5409: Cosponsored - 10/23/79 IRS mileage deductions for volunteers (Box Box 79)
    - HR 5410: Cosponsored - 2/8/80 Federal employee spouse survivor benefits (Box Box 79)
    - HR 5419: Cosponsored - 9/27/79 Byron commemoration for Trail protection (Box Box 79)
    - HR 5461: Cosponsored - 10/25/79 Birthday of Martin Luther King (Box Box 79)
    - HR 5462: Cosponsored - 10/25/79 Federal Employee Occupational Safety (Box Box 79)
    - HR 5510: Cosponsored - 11/5/79 Equal Employment for Handicapped (Box Box 79)
    - HR 5548: Cosponsored - 11/5/79 Medal to Simon Wiesenthal (Box Box 79)
    - HR 5643: Cosponsored - 5/12/80 Rural cooperative Business Income Act (Box Box 79)
    - HR 5660: Cosponsored - 10/23/79 Energy Mobilization Board Substitute (Box Box 79)
    - HR 5687: MacDonald Private Bill (Box Box 80)
    - HR 5704: Cosponsored - 1/31/80 Federal Employee Pay Continuity Bill (Box Box 80)
    - HR 5858: Cosponsored - 11/9/79 Congressional oversight of taxes and regulations. (Box Box 80)
    - HR 5870: Cosponsored - 11/13/79 Career training for air traffic control (Box Box 80)
    - HR 5949: Sponsored - 11/26/79 Amend Antitrust Civil Process Act (Box Box 80)
    - HR 5994: Cosponsored - 1/9/80 Congressional Pay Raise Deferral Act (Box Box 80)
    - HR 5995: Cosponsored - 11/29/79 Continue pay of Federal employees when appropriations delayed (Box Box 80)
    - HR 6065: Cosponsored - 2/20/80 Military leave to Federal employees (Box Box 80)
    - HR 6086: Cosponsored - 3/27/80 Claims against U.S. for evacuation expenses (Box Box 80)
    - HR 6109: Cosponsored - 12/12/79 Higher duties for countries that don't cooperate against violators of international law (Box Box 80)
    - HR 6181: Cosponsored - 5/7/80 Judicial review for Veterans Administration (Box Box 80)
    - HR 6194: Cosponsored - 2/7/80 Community care for elderly (Box Box 80)
    - HR 6270: Cosponsored - 5/27/80 Pay compliance for uniformed services with divorce etc. agreements (Box Box 80)
    - HR 6530: Sponsored - 2/19/80 Limitations on contributions use (Box Box 80)
    - HR 6635: Cosponsored - 2/27/80 Food security reserve of wheat (Box Box 80)
    - HR 6691: Cosponsored - 3/7/80 Discrimination against gasohol (Box Box 80)
    - HR 6722: Cosponsored - 3/6/80 Small Business Motor Fuel Marketer Preservation Act (Box Box 80)
    - HR 6735: Cosponsored - 3/7/80 Medallion for Maggie Lena Walker (Box Box 80)
    - HR 6813: Sponsored - 3/13/80 Energy credit on new homes (Box Box 80)
    - HR 6858: Cosponsored - 4/15/80 Developmentally disabled deductions (Box Box 80)
    - HR 6913: Cosponsored - 3/25/80 Postal employees - safe environment (Box Box 80)
    - HR 6919: Cosponsored - 4/1/80 GSA procurement budget cuts (Box Box 80)
    - HR 7075: Sponsored - 4/16/80 Rehabilitation of Wilson bridge (Box Box 80)
    - HR 7085: Cosponsored - 4/22/80 Relief benefits to hostages (Box Box 80)
    - HR 7086: Cosponsored - 5/28/80 Federal employee pay adjustments (Box Box 80)
    - HR 7157: Cosponsored - 6/6/80 Limitation on Agent Orange claims (Box Box 80)
    - HR 7237: Cosponsored - 6/23/80 Amendments to Rail Act (Box Box 80)
    - HR 7287: Sponsored - Year-end Spending Control Act (Box Box 80)
    - HR 7431: Sponsored - 5/22/80 EPA grants to Upper Occoquan Sewage Authority (Box Box 80)
    - HR 7580: Cosponsored - 6/23/80 Incentives for foreign languages in schools (Box Box 80)
    - HR 7658: Sponsored - 6/25/80 Metro extension study (Box Box 80)
    - HR 7674: Sponsored - 6/26/80 Consultant Reform Act (Box Box 80)
    - HR 7787: Cosponsored - 7/30/80 Assistance to the elderly & low income in heat wave (Box Box 80)
    - HR 7852: Cosponsored - 7/28/80 Aviation Safety and Noise Abatement Act (Box Box 80)
    - HR 7924: Schneider Private Bill (Box Box 80)
    - HR 7974: Cosponsored - 8/20/80 Judicial Councils Reform - Conduct - Disability Act of 1980 (Box Box 80)
    - HR 8081: Cosponsored - 7/29/80 Establish U.S. Holocaust Memorial Council (Box Box 80)
    - HR 8099: Sponsored - 9/10/80 Handicapped Financial Security Act of 1980 (Box Box 80)
    - HR 8163: Cosponsored - 9/18/80 Amendments for the National Capital Transportation Act (Box Box 80)
    - HR 8178: Cosponsored - 9/22/80 Federal District Organization Act 1980 (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 145: Authorizing Sec. of the Interior to establish National Petroleum Reserves (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 270: To establish March 21 of each year as "Earth Day" (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 418: To restore citizenship to R.E. Lee (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 433: Voting representation in Congress for Washington, D.C. residents (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 433: Representations in the District of Columbia (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 533 (534, 536, 535): Renounce first Use Nuclear Weapons (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 579: Resolution designate January 6, 1976 "Haym Salomon Day" (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 579: 1/4/76 as Haym Salomon Day Jewish-American patriots bicentennial year (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 585: Sun. 9/14/75 National St. Elizabeth Seton Day (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 608: To call an Atlantic Convention (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 694: National Family Week (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 777: Thomas Jefferson Day (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 211: Sponsored - 1/31/77 June 1977 National Graduation Class of '77 month (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 284: Cosponsored - 2/24/77 Protection of international waters (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 404: Sponsored - 4/21/77 National Graduating Class of '77 Month (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 521: Cosponsored - 6/15/77 Citizenship to Jefferson Davis (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 540: Cosponsored - 6/30/77 Pacific/ Asian American Heritage Week (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 625: Cosponsored - To authorize White House Conference on Families (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 634: Cosponsored - Establish Yorktown Bicentennial Commission (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 710: Sponsored - 2/1/78 National Vocational Education Week (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 719: Cosponsored - 2/6/78 Resolution proclaiming 5/3/78 "Sun Day" (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 938: Cosponsored - 5/24/78 National Grandparents' Day (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 946: Cosponsored - 5/31/78 National Guard Day - Oct. 7, 1978 (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 950: Cosponsored - 5/31/78 Promote the recognition of American "National Family Week" (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 971: Cosponsored - 6/12/78 "National Lupus Week" (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 1022: Cosponsored - 6/22/78 "National Port Week" (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 1041: Cosponsored - 6/29/78 Restore citizenship to Jefferson F. Davis (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 1046: Cosponsored - 6/29/78 National POW-MIA Recognition Day, 7/18/79 (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 19: Cosponsored - 3/7/79 National Lupus Week (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 68: Cosponsored - 5/17/79 National Family Week (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 198: Cosponsored - 10/18/79 Designates "Teacher Day, U.S.A." (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 205: (Bunche) Cosponsor (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 220: Cosponsored - 1/23/80 "National Energy Education Day" (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 229: Cosponsored - 5/13/79 National Free Enterprise Day (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 244: Cosponsored - 6/19/79 National Grandparents' Day (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 251: Cosponsored - 6/4/79 Developing better statistical data (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 255: Cosponsored - 3/13/79 "National Medic Alert Week" (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 262: Cosponsored - 5/7/79 National Museum Day (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 263: Cosponsored - 10/16/79 Designates National Farm Workers Week (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 267: Cosponsored - 2/25/80 Teacher Day, U.S.A. (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 291: Cosponsored - 4/11/79 Including energy prices in President's anti- inflation limits (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 303: Cosponsored - 5/9/79 National Port Week (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 347: Cosponsored - 5/30/79 Encourage international cooperation in meeting expenses of Egyptian-Israel Peace Treaty (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 372: Cosponsored - 9/25/79 "Organization for Rehabilitation through Training Centennial Day" (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 389: Cosponsored - 9/5/79 Sept. 1980 as National Rehabilitation Month (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 414: Cosponsored - 1/28/80 "National Bicycling Day" (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 416: Cosponsored - 12/6/79 National Postal Workers' Recognition Day (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 417: Cosponsored - 1/28/80 "National Porcelain Art Month" (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 442: Cosponsored - 2/25/80 National Athletic Boosters Week (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 463: Cosponsored - 1/30/80 "National Diabetes Week" (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 470: Cosponsored - 12/20/79 Helen Keller Day, June 27, 1980 (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 474: Cosponsored - 3/25/80 Jewish Heritage Week (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 477: Cosponsored - 1/22/80 Honoring the memory of Walt Disney (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 507: Cosponsored - 3/6/80 National P.O.W.-M.I.A. Recognition Day (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 518: Cosponsored - 4/14/80 Iwo Jima reunion - national historic event (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 529: Cosponsored - 4/1/80 200th anniversary of Victory at Yorktown (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 531: Cosponsored - 5/15/80 Disapproving of import fee on crude oil and gas (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 551: Cosponsored - 6/19/80 "National Port Week" (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 560: 5/29/80 National Agriculture Day -- Mar 19, 1981 (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 564: Cosponsored - 6/12/80 "National Italian-American Day" Sons of Italy (Box Box 80)
    - HJ Res 578: Cosponsored - 7/10/80 "Jack Jouett Day" June 4, 1981 (Box Box 80)
    - H.Con.Res. 75: Condemning a limitation of 5% on Social Security this July (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 222: Evacuation of American citizens from Vietnam (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 244: Safety of American nationals in Vietnam (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 249: Direct Sec. of Defense to operate commissary store (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 551: Support of Brussels Conference on Soviet Jewry (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 744: Study of impact Federal land on local government (Spellman) (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 34: Cosponsored - 1/25/78 Asking Pres. Carter to start a framework for cooperation with Mexico (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 62: Cosponsored - 1/17/77 Statue of the Reverend Martin Luther King, Jr. (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 97: Cosponsored - 2/1/77 Harassment of Soviet Jews (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 148: Cosponsored - 3/9/77 Study impact federally-owned land (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 175: Cosponsored - 3/23/77 Dr. S. Kovalev/ USSR/ Cornell University (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 521: Sponsored - 3/14/78 Condemnation of PLO for Attacks on Israel (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 630: Cosponsored - 5/22/78 Congress not in favor export of uranium to India (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res 722: Cosponsored - 9/20/78 Concern for residents of South Africa "Crossroads" (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 21: Sponsored - 1/15/79 Invite Chief Justice report on judiciary state (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 80: Cosponsored - 1/15/79 To authorize the commissioning of a statue or bust of Martin Luther King, Jr. to put in Capitol (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 90: Cosponsored - 3/2/79 Air Force Academy Commendation (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 103: Cosponsored - 6/19/79 Asking the President to communicate our feelings on religious freedom in Russia (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 121: Cosponsored - 5/16/79 1979 Irish Resolution (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 122: Cosponsored - 5/17/79 Asking Great Britain to start a new initiative for Ireland (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 158: Cosponsored - 7/10/79 Commemorative stamp for Philip Mazzei (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 167: Cosponsored - 7/27/79 Soviet nondelivery of international mail (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 190: Cosponsored - 9/20/79 Welcoming Pope to U.S. (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 202: Cosponsored - 10/24/79 U.S.S.R. should release Ida Nudel (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 225: Cosponsored - 2/7/80 Social Security benefits exempt (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 245: Cosponsored - 1/21/80 Summer Olympic Relocation (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 252: Cosponsored - 2/7/80 Earth Day April 22, 1980 (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 259: Cosponsored - 1/24/80 Release Sakharov from internal exile (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 265: Cosponsored - 2/4/80 Soviet Release of Sakharov (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 267: Cosponsored - 1/30/80 Gratitude for Canada for Americans' safety (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 272: Cosponsored - 2/5/80 Release Sakharov - human rights in U.S.S.R. (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 301: Cosponsored - 3/26/80 Resolution in support of foreign languages in schools (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 338: Cosponsored - 5/21/80 Obligation to standard of living for elderly (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 365: Sponsored - 6/17/80 Save Postal Service and retired Military & Federal employees (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 391: Cosponsored - 7/29/80 Helsinki Delegation should raise rights (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 395: Cosponsored - 7/30/80 Red Cross visits to hostages (Box Box 81)
    - H.Con.Res. 409: Cosponsored - 8/21/80 Concern for Soviet Protestant Christians (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 335: Select commission to study M.I.A.s (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 361: A resolution relating to food assistance - Cambodia (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 370: Public Television in the House 1st session 94th Congress (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 457: May 12, 1975 Not approve funds for renovating Lorton (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 466: To open conference meetings to public (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 496: Establish select commission - missing servicemen - Asia (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 498: Committee to investigate John F. Kennedy's death (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 569: Amend House rules verbatim floor remarks recorded (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 588: Air travel reimbursement for certain House employees (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 678: Disapprove threat by United Nations to expel Israel (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 678: Israel in the United Nations (Box Box 81)